flyffworld.com 2008-12-17

# FlyFFWorld.com - Terms Of Service

FlyFFWorld.com is in no ways part of Aeonsoft or Gala-Net Inc, its affiliates, successors, parents, subsidiaries, assigns, licensees, and designees. The claims, or comments that we make do not reflect that of Aeonsoft or Gala-Net Inc By using FlyFFWorld.com you must obliged to rules and regulations which you must fully agree to, upon using the service in anyway's. 

Please read the Terms of Service carefully. By using the Service, you agree to the terms and conditions outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the Service. FlyFFWorld.com reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of the Terms of Service at any time, in its sole discretion (Without You Knowing). The service may be updated, at any time without prior notice. It is your duty to read up follow the rules and terms of service at all times. If you continue to use the Service after FlyFFWorld.com has posted changes to the Terms of Service, it means you have accepted the changed terms. 

**Disclaimer of Warranties**  
The service is provided to you (The Visitor, Member, Guest) on an "As Is" and "AS AVAILABLE." basis. Which means, we can discontinue the service anytime. FlyFFWorld.com does not guarantee, the service to be up all the times, or at anytime. We may impose limits on the service at any time to you without prior notice. FlyFFWorld.com does not guarantee or warrant that any files available for downloading through the Service will be free of infectious viruses or other codes that may contain contaminating or destructive properties to your computer. 

FlyFFWorld.com does not warrant that any tutorials taught will be guarantee to render the desired results. 

FlyFFWorld.com does not warrant that all/any links to be working at any time/all and are only brought to you on an as is/as available basis. 

**Links to Third Party Sites**  
Any third-party sites to which the Service may link are not under FlyFFWorld.com's control, and FlyFFWorld.com does not assume any responsibility or liability for any information, content, communications or materials available on such third-party sites. Links to third party sites are only here for convenience reasons only. 

**Copyright**  
FlyFFWorld.com is copyrighted and protected by the law. You may not copy, redistribute, or rewrite any of the files, tutorials, images or any type of content within FlyFFWorld.com without prior written knowledge and consent from FlyFFWorld.com. If you fail to obliged by this rule you are breaking the law and FlyFFWorld.com has the right to take action and report you to the proper authorities. 

Images that are in used by FlyFFWorld.com maybe copyrighted and FlyFFWorld.com does not claim these as it owns. All images maybe copyrighted by third parties or their respective owners. 

**Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

We only collect information that you yourself provide to us when you join one of membership features, such as our forum. The information we collect are your name, e-mail address, and optional information such as your ICQ number or AIM screename. 

The forum system uses cookies to store information on your local computer. These cookies do not contain any of the information you have entered above; they serve only to improve your viewing pleasure. The e-mail address is used only for confirming your registration details and password (and for sending new passwords should you forget your current one). They also do not collect any other information on your computer. We are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. 

We do not sell or give your personal information to any sites. Your information is safely protected and will never be given out unless you yourself ask so. 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

Third Partied services that are in used by FlyFFWorld.com may collect other information but not information such as credit card numbers and bank account numbers. FlyFFWorld.com also displays advertisement that may collect personal information but not information such as credit card numbers and bank account numbers.

If you have any further question regarding your privacy please contact us. 

**Liability**  
FlyFFWorld.com is not liable for any codes that may disrupt, damage, or destroy your properties, computers, software's, or programs. You use the codes at your own risk. These codes are only used for educational purposes only and not meant as a weapon to disrupt, damage, or destroy your properties. 

FlyFFWorld.com provides a forum service which is monitored. Any personal information that you give/post about yourself in any part of the forum will not be protected. You post at your own risk. We are not responsible for any objectionable material posted by Members that you may encounter while using the Forum Service. 

We do not allow selling or trading of flyff accounts on this site or forum. We can not be held liable for any type of scams.

We will never disclosed to any third party without your consent however we cannot be held responsible for any hacking attempt that may lead to the data being compromised. 

**Acknowledgement**  
By the using the service in any ways, you agree fully to the terms and condition listed above.
